In this segment, we're going to learn a little bit about our bindings, the things that hold your feet to your board.
They?re pretty important.
You want a good relationship with them.
This here is their highback.
This would be your heel strap and toe strap.
These are your ladders.
To strap in, simply put your foot inside the binding.
Connect the ratchet to the ladder and strap it down.
You want a good amount of pressure on both of them so they're really holding your binding, your foot to the binding.
You don't want any loose movement.
If you strap them in too loose, you?re not going to have a good connection with your snowboard.
It's not going to respond to your actions.
So, you want to go ahead and make sure they're in there solid.
And that's how you strap on a binding.